I wanted to ask how you feel about a
хотел спросить как вы относитесь к
special military operation any
специальной военной операции любые
military action is bad It
боевые действия - это плохо Ты
turns out that Russia did the wrong thing by
получается Россия неправильно сделает
attacking Ukraine and Ukraine
что напала на Украину а а Украина
did the right thing by unpacking it and get out
правильно делала что а распаковали вали
Well then how do you think that it was
Ну то вы как получается считаете что
right to do that Russia attacked
правильно сделать что Россия напала на
Ukraine
Украину
Well, well, well  defend your interests
да Надо же отстаивать свои интересы
What always here Europe you are
Какие всегда вот Европа вы вот
striving for NATO yes So what difference does it make to you
стремитесь в НАТО да Так и что вам кая
NATO told us 30 years ago we
НАТО говорила ещё 30 лет назад мы не
will not expand to the east
будем расширяться на восток
they How old are you I am 30 30 yes that is
они Вам сколько лет мне 30 30 да то есть
when you were born NATO said that we will not
когда вы родились НАТО сказало что мы не
expand  to the east yes
расширим на восток да
yes with the fall of the Berlin wall
да с падением берлинской стены хотят
people want to join NATO what difference does it make
люди выйти в НАТО входят какая разница
for the security of our for the security of
для безопасности нашей для безопасности
whom our country and what's wrong with your
кого нашей страны а что там с вашей
country Are you afraid of NATO it is
страной не так Вы что боитесь НАТО это
now the largest military bloc
сейчас самый крупный военный блок то
that is NATO should have attacked you  That's
есть НАТО надо на вас нападать было Вот
what I can't understand. NATO is deploying.
и что я не могу понять НАТО же размещает
Why, if you are such a state
Для чего если вы настолько государство
that Ukraine is shelling you. For example, it's
что вас Украина Вот например
not even NATO that's shelling you, but Ukraine is
обстреливает даже не НАТО а Украина так
shelling your Belgorod region,
обстреливает вашу Белгородскую область
Kursk, Bryansk, and today
так курскую брянскую вон сегодня
they flew into St. Petersburg.  flights were cancelled Yes
прилетали в в Питере отменяли полёты Да
because it flew there to the far end and it
из-за того что долетела туда доле а
was just there lo there lo yes And what was
просто там ло было там было ло да А что
flying there that they closed the airport there
там летало что закрыли аэропорт там
were exercises to Moscow yes it flew Yes it flies it
учения были в Москву да летала Да летает
flies and you can't do anything And
летает и вы ничего не можете сделать А
what is it Well you say that  right
что так Ну вы говорите что правильно
Russia attacked Ukraine for what purpose
Россия напала на Украину вам для чего
specifically here in your kitchen
это конкретно вот вам на вашей кухне
If you now You if you now
Если вы сейчас Вы если вы сейчас
send drones as you say all the way
беспилотники посылаете как вы говорите
to St. Petersburg then with the same
до самого Питера то таким же с таким же
success you can from the border
успехом вы с границы
How many kilometers from St. Petersburg to NATO
може Сколько от Питера до НАТО
near the Leningrad region  there is a
километров у Ленинградской области есть
border with NATO and that is the Leningrad
граница с НАТО и то есть Ленинградская
region it is already right next to NATO What does
область она уже впритык к НАТО Причём
Ukraine have to do with it from Ukraine to the Leningrad
тут Украина от Украины до Ленинградской
region and even to the Moscow region is
области да и до Московской области
further than from, uh, Latvia, Lithuania, Estonia And
дальше чем от ээ Латвии Литвы Эстонии А
now there will also be Finland there and Sweden
теперь ещё будет Финляндия там и Швеция
yes
да